{
  "response_code": 0,
  "results": [
    {
      "category": "Celebrities",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "Who played Jack Dawson in the movie 'Titanic'?",
      "correct_answer": "Leonardo%20DiCaprio",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Brad%20Pitt",
        "Tom%20Cruise",
        "Johnny%20Depp"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Celebrities",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "Which actress starred in the movie 'Pretty Woman'?",
      "correct_answer": "Julia%20Roberts",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Cameron%20Diaz",
        "Meryl%20Streep",
        "Reese%20Witherspoon"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Celebrities",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "Who is known for playing the character Iron Man in the Marvel Cinematic Universe?",
      "correct_answer": "Robert%20Downey%20Jr.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Chris%20Hemsworth",
        "Chris%20Evans",
        "Mark%20Ruffalo"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Celebrities",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "Which pop star is known for the song 'Umbrella'?",
      "correct_answer": "Rihanna",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Beyonce",
        "Lady%20Gaga",
        "Adele"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Celebrities",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "Who won an Academy Award for Best Actor for his role in 'The Revenant'?",
      "correct_answer": "Leonardo%20DiCaprio",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Tom%20Hanks",
        "Brad%20Pitt",
        "Christian%20Bale"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Celebrities",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "Which actor starred as Captain Jack Sparrow in the 'Pirates of the Caribbean' series?",
      "correct_answer": "Johnny%20Depp",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Orlando%20Bloom",
        "Keira%20Knightley",
        "Geoffrey%20Rush"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Celebrities",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "Who is the lead vocalist of the band 'Queen'?",
      "correct_answer": "Freddie%20Mercury",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "David%20Bowie",
        "Mick%20Jagger",
        "Elton%20John"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Celebrities",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "Which actress starred in the movie 'Mean Girls'?",
      "correct_answer": "Lindsay%20Lohan",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Emma%20Watson",
        "Amanda%20Seyfried",
        "Scarlett%20Johansson"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Celebrities",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "Who is known for being the founder of Facebook?",
      "correct_answer": "Mark%20Zuckerberg",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Bill%20Gates",
        "Jeff%20Bezos",
        "Elon%20Musk"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Celebrities",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "Which actor played the character Neo in 'The Matrix' trilogy?",
      "correct_answer": "Keanu%20Reeves",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Tom%20Cruise",
        "Brad%20Pitt",
        "Johnny%20Depp"
      ]
    }
  ]
}
